American Civil Liberties Union Records: Subgroup 2, Audiovisual Materials Series, 1947-1995: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 6, Audio-Visual materials, 1930-1995; 70 boxes, 1 folder
  - VHS Cassette Tapes, 1979 March-1995; portion of 16 boxes
    - ABC World News Tonight, NBC Nightly News, Good Morning America, Drunk Driving Roadblocks; Nadine Strossen, 1990 June 15; 1990-19; portion of 1 box (Box 2044)
    - The Koppel Report, "Drugs, Crime, and Doing Time"; None, 1990 September 5; 1990-20; portion of 1 box (Box 2044)
    - America's Drug Forum, A War on Drugs or a War on Constitutional Rights?; Ira Glasser, 1990 September; 1990-21; portion of 1 box (Box 2044)
    - Firing Line, Death Penalty; Henry Schwarzschild, 1990 October 6; 1990-22; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - Copy of Firing Line, Death Penalty; Henry Schwarzschild, 1990 October 6; portion of 1 box (Box 5676)
    - ABC World News Tonight, Tacit Speech Codes; Brady Williamson, 1990 November 1; 1990-22; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - CNBC-McLaughlin, The ACLU's Integrity; Ira Glasser, 1990 October 1; 1990-23; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - ACLU Press Conference after Rust v. Sullivan, Abortion Counseling; Rachael Pine and Laurence Tribe, 1990 October 3; 1990-24; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - C-SPAN Coverage, Rust v. Sullivan; Rachael Pine, 1990 October 3; 1990-25; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - MacNeil-Lehrer News Hour, Rust v. Sullivan; Laurence Tribe, 1990 October 3; 1990-26; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - Sonya Live on CNN, Black Male Only Schools; Norman Siegel, 1990 November; 1990-27; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - ACLU Press Conference, A State of Emergency in the American Workplace; Lew Maltby, 1990 December 1; 1990-28; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - First Amendment Congress, 45 Words of Freedom: The Meaning of the First Amendment; Allan Adler, 1990; 1990-29; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - Idaho CLU Appearance, Anti-abortion Laws; Jack Van Valkenbergh, 1990; 1990-30; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - ABC World News Tonight, Civil Liberties in the Persian Gulf; Ira Glasser, 1991 January 28; 1991-1; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - MacNeil-Lehrer Report, Police Brutality in L.A.; Ramona Ripston, 1991 March 15; 1991-1; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - ABC News 20/20, Gays in the Military, 1991 March 8; 1991-2; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - Crossfire, Justify the Video: Obscenity in Madonna's Video; Danny Goldberg, 1991 March 18; 1991-3; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - CBS Evening News, Police Brutality in L.A.; Ramona Ripston, 1991 March 20; 1991-4; portion of 1 box (Box 2045)
    - Sonya Live on CNN, Coerced Confessions; Steve Shapiro, 1991 March 26; 1991-5; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - Donahue Show, Forced Contraception; Julie Mertus, 1991 March 28; 1991-5; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - CNN Crier and Co., Victim's Rights; Vivian Berger, 1991 April 16; 1991-6; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - Thirteen Live, Children's Rights; Marcia Robinson Lowry, 1991 May 15; 1991-7; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - C-SPAN Coverage, Rust v. Sullivan Press Conference; Rachael Pine, 1991 May 23; 1991-8; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - PBS Special: Safe Speech, Free Speech and the University, Hate Speech on Campus; Nadine Strossen, 1991 June 6; 1991-9; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - ABC World News Tonight, Black Male Only Academies; Howard Simon, 1991 August 14; 1991-9; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - CBS News Nightwatch, Racist Speech on Campus; Nadine Strossen, 1991 August; 1991-10; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - ABC World News Tonight, Lifestyle Discrimination; Lew Maltby, 1991 September 11; 1991-11; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - Heart of the Matter (ABC Sunday Morning Talk Show), Drug and Impairment Testing; John Rosenthal, 1991 September 15; 1991-12; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - C-SPAN Coverage, The ACLU's Changing Strategy; Steve Shapiro, 1991 October 3; 1991-13; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - Press Club Briefing, The ACLU's Changing Strategy; Legal and Project Directors (full length), 1991 October 3; 1991-14A; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - Press Club Briefing, The ACLU's Changing Strategy; Legal and Project Directors (cut 1), 1991 October 3; 1991-14B; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - Press Club Briefing, The ACLU's Changing Strategy; Legal and Project Directors (cut 2 and 3), 1991 October 3; 1991-14C; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - Sonya Live on CNN, Gay and Lesbian Weddings and Religious Freedom; Bill Rubenstein, 1991 October 7; 1991-15; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - Larry King Live on CNN, Sexual Harassment in the Workplace; Nadine Strossen, 1991 October 1; 1991-15; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - Sonya Live on CNN, Lee v. Weisman (Graduation Prayers); Arthur Spitzer, 1991 November 1; 1991-16; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - MacNeil-Lehrer, Lee v. Weisman (Graduation Prayers); Nadine Strossen, 1991 November 6; 1991-16; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - Pozner/Donahue, The Sorry State of the Bill of Rights in America; Ira Glasser, 1991 November 3; 1991-17; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - Firing Line, The Bill of Rights; Ira Glasser, 1991 November 13; 1991-17; portion of 1 box (Box 2046)
    - C-SPAN Coverage, Guam Obstetricians v. ADA; Anita Arriola, 1991 November 4; 1991-18; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - CNN Coverage, Reproductive Freedom: Planned Parenthood v. Casey; Kitty Kolbet, 1991 November 7; 1991-19; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - Press Conference, ACLU Arts Censorship Project, 1991 December 9; 1991-20; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - NBC Nightly News, Hate Speech on Campuses; Nadine Strossen, 1991 December 9; 1991-21; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - CNN World Today, Bicentennial of the Bill of Rights; Nadine Strossen, 1991 December 14; 1991-21; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - NBC Sunday Today, Bicentennial of the Bill of Rights; Ira Glasser, 1991 December 1; 1991-21; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - Crossfire, The Bill of Rights, Ira Glasser, 1991 December 2; 1991-22; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - MacNeil Lehrer, Stroh's Sexual Harassment Suit; Matthew Stark, 1991 December 2; 1991-23; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - Sonya Live on CNN, Sexually Explicit Speech; Marjorie Heins, 1992 January 2; 1992-1; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - Crossfire, David Duke's Candidacy; Steve Shapiro, 1992 January 3; 1992-1; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - NBC Today Show, Places to Smoke; Lew Maltby, 1992 January 3; 1992-2; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - Sonya Live on CNN, Reproductive Freedom; Kathryn Kolbert, 1992 January 13; 1992-3; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - UC/Davis, Free Speech on Campus; Nadine Strossen, 1992 January 14; 1992-4; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - Oprah Winfrey, Foster Care, Adam Mann; None, 1992 January 15; 1992-5; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - ABC News 20/20, Workplace Lifestyle Discrimination; Lew Maltby, 1992 January 17; 1992-5; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - CNN Daywatch, Casey v. Planned Parenthood, 1992 January 21; 1992-6; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - NBC Nightly News and Charlie Rose, Casey v. Planned Parenthood; Kathryn Kolbert and Nadine Strossen, 1992 January 21; 1992-7; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - ABC News and Nightline, Casey v. Planned Parenthood; Kathryn Kolbert, 1992 January 21; 1992-8; portion of 1 box (Box 2047)
    - Columbia University Seminars, That Delicate Balance II Our Bill of Rights and the First Amendment and Hate Speech, 1992 January 29; 1992-9; portion of 1 box (Box 2048)
    - Keppler Associates, Censorship; Strossen/Meese Debate, 1992 January 30; 1992-10; portion of 1 box (Box 2048)
    - Larry King Live on CNN, Pornography-Victim Compensation; Nadine Strossen, 1992 January 31; 1992-11; portion of 1 box (Box 2048)
    - PBS Bill Moyers Special, Hate on Trial; Norman Siegel, 1992 February 4; 1992-12; portion of 1 box (Box 2048)
    - Charlie Rose, Clarence Thomas' Jurisprudence; John Powell, 1992 February 28; 1992-13; portion of 1 box (Box 2048)
    - ACLU/NC Video Clips, Various, 1992 February 3-March 3; 1992-14; portion of 1 box (Box 2048)
    - Larry King Live on CNN, Police Reform in L.A.; Ramona Ripston, 1992 March 13; 1992-15; portion of 1 box (Box 2048)
    - WVCLU Video Clips, Various; Various, 1992 June 9-30; 1992-16; portion of 1 box (Box 2048)
    - CNN, "Kris Hansen and Clint Bullock", 1992 April 1; 1992-17; portion of 1 box (Box 2048)
    - CBS Evening News, AMA Report on Drug Testing; Lew Maltby, 1992 April 2; 1992-18; portion of 1 box (Box 2048)
    - March for Women's Lives; Nadine Strossen Remarks, 1992 April 5; 1992-19; portion of 1 box (Box 2048)
    - Sonya Live on CNN, Forced Contraception; Lynn Paltrow, 1992 April 27; 1992-20; portion of 1 box (Box 2048)
    - Charlie Rose, Rodney King Verdict; Nadine Strossen, Roy Innes, David Lewis and Marty Adelman, 1992 April 29; 1992-21; portion of 1 box (Box 2048)
    - Donohue, Rodney King Verdict; Ira Glasser, Al Sharpton and John Conyers, 1992 April 30; 1992-22; portion of 1 box (Box 2048)
    - Charlie Rose, Communitarianism; Nadine Strossen and Amitai Etzioni, 1992 May 18; 1992-23; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - KING-TV Seattle News, "Whose Life is It?", 1992 May 18 - 20; 1992-24; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - Good Afternoon, Syracuse, NY; Nadine Strossen, 1992 May 20; 1992-25; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - NBC Sunday Today, Communitarianism; Nadine Strossen and Amitai Etzioni, 1992 May 24; 1992-26; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - Sonya Live on CNN, Anti-Stalking Laws; Loren Siegel, 1992 June 8; 1992-27; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - CBS The People, HIV: Should Your Doctor be Tested?; Liz Cooper, 1992 June 13; 1992-28; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - CBS Morning News, Anti-Stalking Laws; Loren Siegel, 1992 June 18; 1992-29; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - CNN Crier and Co., Supreme Court Term 1991-92; Nadine Strossen, 1992 June 26; 1992-30; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - PBS, The Fourth Amendment: Search and Seizure; Nadine Strossen, 1992 October 5; 1992-31; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - ACLU News Conference, Orlando, FL, 1992 October 2; 1992-32; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - A New Social Agenda?; Jerry Falwell and Nadine Strossen, 1992 November 1; 1992-33; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - Clemency Video for Governor Wilson; Robert Harris, 1992; 1992-34; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - Hard Drugs, Hard Choices Part 1, 1992; 1992-35A; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - Hard Drugs, Hard Choices Part 2, 1992; 1992-35B; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - Hoover Institution, Searching for Alternative Drug Control Policy in the U.S., 1992; 1992-36; portion of 1 box (Box 2049)
    - PBS Frontline, The Death of Nancy Cruzan, 1992; 1992-37; portion of 1 box (Box 2050)
    - Keeping Freedom's Flame Alive, ACLU Box, 1995; 1995-1; portion of 1 box (Box 2050)
  - Audio Tapes, 1961 March-1989; portion of 8 boxes
    - Audio Tapes (7 Inch Reels), 1961 March-1976; 2 boxes
      - Michael Harrington and Fulton Lewis III Debate at the University of Connecticut, 1961 March; 1; portion of 1 box (Box 2051)
      - Michael Harrington and Fulton Lewis III Debate at the University of Connecticut (cont'd), 1961 March; 2; portion of 1 box (Box 2051)
      - What is Un-American? TV Debate with David Susskind as Moderator, Fulton Lewis III, M. Stanton Evans Godfrey Schmidt, Arthur Cohen, John H. Faulk and Frank Donner, 1961 October; portion of 1 box (Box 2051)
      - Mazey and Fulton Lewis III Debate at Delta College Michigan, 1963 March 21; 4; portion of 1 box (Box 2051)
      - "Hate is a Wrong-Way Street" WINS Documentary Editorial, Part I of II, 08/25, no year; 5; portion of 1 box (Box 2051)
      - "Hate is a Wrong-Way Street" WINS Documentary Editorial, Part II of II, 08/27, no year; 6; portion of 1 box (Box 2051)
      - Lawyers Constitutional Defense Committee - Publicity - Blurb sheets, files, 1966 April; 7; portion of 1 box (Box 2051)
      - ACLU Biennial Conference, Loeb Student Center New York University, 1970 June 03; 8; portion of 1 box (Box 2051)
      - ACLU Biennial Conference, Loeb Student Center New New York University, 1970 June 03; 9; portion of 1 box (Box 2051)
      - ACLU Biennial Conference, Womankind - Sue Ross on Women and Criminal Law, 1970 June 04; 10; portion of 1 box (Box 2051)
      - ACLU Biennial Conference, Loeb Student Center New York University - Afternoon Sessions, 1970 June 06; 11; portion of 1 box (Box 2051)
      - ACLU Biennial Conference, Loeb Student Center New, 1970 June 06; 12; portion of 1 box (Box 2051)
      - Changes Part I-A, 1970 November 22; 13; portion of 1 box (Box 2051)
      - Changes Part I-B, 1970 November 22; 14; portion of 1 box (Box 2051)
      - Changes Part II-A, 1970 November 22; portion of 1 box (Box 2052)
      - Board Meeting - Morning and Afternoon Sessions, 1970 September 29; 16; portion of 1 box (Box 2052)
      - Board Meeting - Impeachment Sides 1 and 2, 1974 June 12; 17; portion of 1 box (Box 2052)
      - Board Meeting - Impeachment Sides 3 and 4, 1974 June 12; 18; portion of 1 box (Box 2052)
      - Board Meeting - Impeachment Sides 5 and 6, 1974 June 12; 19; portion of 1 box (Box 2052)
      - Board Meeting, 1976 October 02; 20; portion of 1 box (Box 2052)
      - Board Meeting, 1976 October 03; 21; portion of 1 box (Box 2052)
      - Board Meeting, 1976 November; 22; portion of 1 box (Box 2052)
      - Board Meeting, 1976 December; 23; portion of 1 box (Box 2052)
      - Interview with Grooer or Butner on Behavior Modification, undated; 24; portion of 1 box (Box 2052)
      - no title(s), undated; 25-27; portion of 1 box (Box 2052)
    - Audio Tapes (5 Inch Reels), 1961 November 28-1970 August; portion of 1 box
      - Bill of Rights Radio Spots, 1961 November 28; 1; portion of 1 box (Box 2053)
      - ACLU Public Service Announcements, 1970 August; 2; portion of 1 box (Box 2053)
      - ACLU Public Service Announcements, undated; 3; portion of 1 box (Box 2053)
      - Public Service Announcements - New Rochelle, NY, undated; 4; portion of 1 box (Box 2053)
      - no title, undated; 5; portion of 1 box (Box 2053)
      - no title, undated; 6; portion of 1 box (Box 2053)
      - Roger Baldwin, Seg. 2-3, Show #148, undated; 7; portion of 1 box (Box 2053)
    - Audio Tapes (3 Inch Reels), 1970 January 21; portion of 1 box
      - CBS TV interview with Roger Baldwin, 1970 January 21; 1; portion of 1 box (Box 2053)
    - Audio Cassette Tapes, 1976-1989; portion of 5 boxes
      - Biennial Conference, 1985; portion of 2 boxes
        - Opening Session; Roland O'Hare and Norman Dorsen, 1985 June; 1; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Assaults on Bill of Rights; Ira Glasser, 1985 June; 2; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Organizational Issues; Panel, 1985 June; 3; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Abortion/Anti-Abortion Rights; G. Thomas, M.P. Hames and A. Locklear, 1985 June; 4; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Women, Pornography and the 1st Amendment; J. Crawford, C. MacKinnon and H. Pilpel, 1985 June; 5; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Women, Pornography and the 1st Amendment; J. Crawford, C. MacKinnon and H. Pilpel (Copy), 1985; portion of 1 box (Box 5676)
          Copy on 2 cds.
        - Establishment and Free Exercise Clauses; Rev. Dean Kelley, 1985 June; 6A; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Establishment and Free Exercise Clauses; Rev. Dean Kelley, 1985 June; 6B; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Gay Rights; D. Waxse, M. Kegel and A. Rubenfeld, 1985 June; 7; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Gay Rights; D. Waxse, M. Kegel and A. Rubenfeld (Copy), 1985; portion of 1 box (Box 5676)
        - Women's Rights; T. Young, I. Pinzler and S. Post, 1985 June; 8; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Crime in the Streets; S. Walker, L. Siegel and P. Rosner, 1985 June; 9; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Capital Punishment; M. Gaines, G. Kendall, D. Davidson and H. Schwarzschild, 1985 June; 10; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Book Censorship; P. Meyer, L. Katz and M. Weidler, 1985 June; 11; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Poor People's Rights; R. Carrigan, P. Strum, G. Guerrero, L. Monroe and R. Ripston, 1985 June; 12; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Government Surveillance; R. Schoen, J. Berman, and J. Miller, 1985 June; 13; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Immigration Rights; M. Gale, W. Henderson and M. Metcalfe, 1985 June; 14; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Withholding and Receiving Medical Treatment; M. Gallwey, V. Milstein and M. Gradison, 1985 June; 15; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Children's Rights; L. Grossman, C. Hansen and B. Steinhardt, 1985 June; 16; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Rights of the Disabled; J. Fiske, A. Gartner and S. Pedler, 1985 June; 17; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Race Discrimination; E. Feingold, R. Larson and S. Kurjiaka, 1985 June; 18; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - The New Imperial Presidency; A. Lewis, 1985 June; 19; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Abuses in the Workplace; Ed Asner and Panel, 1985 June; 20A; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Abuses in the Workplace; Ed Asner and Panel, 1985 June; 20B; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Nuclear Arms/Civil Liberties; W. Lynch, M. Schachter and J. McTerran, 1985 June; 21A; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Nuclear Arms/Civil Liberties; W. Lynch, M. Schachter and J. McTerran, 1985 June; 21B; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - International Law and Civil Liberties; F. Haiman and P. Hoffman, 1985 June; 22; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Final Plenary Session; Rolland O'Hare, 1985 June; 23A; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Final Plenary Session; Rolland O'Hare, 1985 June; 23B; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Final Plenary Session; Rolland O'Hare, 1985 June; 23C; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Final Plenary Session; Rolland O'Hare, 1985 June; 23D; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Lawyers Meeting, 1985 June 12; 24A; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Lawyers Meeting, 1985 June 12; 24B; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
        - Board of Directors Meeting, Tapes A-E, 1985; 25-29; portion of 1 box (Box 2054)
      - Biennial Conference, 1987; portion of 2 boxes
        - Opening Plenary Session, dates not examined; 1A; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Forums for Protecting Rights - Session 1, The Courts, dates not examined; 2A; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Forums for Protecting Rights - Session 1, The Courts, dates not examined; 2B; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Original Intent - Interpretation and the Constitutional Vision, dates not examined; 3; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Death Penalty, dates not examined; 4; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Immigration Rights, dates not examined; 5; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Separation of Church and State, dates not examined; 6; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Reproductive Freedom, dates not examined; 7; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Rights of the Disabled, dates not examined; 8; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Lawyers Meeting, dates not examined; 9A; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Lawyers Meeting, dates not examined; 9B; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Forums for Protecting Rights - Session 2 Public Opinion, dates not examined; 10; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Forums for Protecting Rights - Session 3 The Legislatures, dates not examined; 11; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Student's Rights in Schools, dates not examined; 12; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Sex Discrimination, dates not examined; 13; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Lesbian and Gay Rights, dates not examined; 14; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Information and Privacy, dates not examined; 15; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Information and Privacy Copy, 1987; portion of 1 box (Box 5676)
        - Drug Testing, dates not examined; 16; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Prisoners' Rights, dates not examined; 17; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Civil Liberties and Hysteria, dates not examined; 18; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Civil Liberties in the Constitution's Third Century, dates not examined; 19; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Constitution and White House - Secrecy v. Accountability, dates not examined; 20; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Economic Rights, dates not examined; 21; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Race Discrimination, dates not examined; 22; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Censorship and Pornography, dates not examined; 23; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Censorship and Pornography Copy, 1987; portion of 1 box (Box 5676)
          Copy on 2 cds
        - Children's Rights, dates not examined; 24; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - AIDS Discrimination, dates not examined; 25; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Banquet, dates not examined; 26; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Final Plenary Session, dates not examined; 27A; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Final Plenary Session, dates not examined; 27B; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
        - Freedom Brunch, dates not examined; 28; portion of 1 box (Box 2055)
      - Biennial Conference, 1989; 1 box
        - Today's Challenge to the Bill of Rights, dates not examined; 1; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Reproductive Freedom, dates not examined; 2A-2B; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Surrogate Parenting, dates not examined; 3; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Death Penalty, dates not examined; 4; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Censorship, dates not examined; 5; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Prisoners' Rights, dates not examined; 6; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Privacy, Technology and Civil Liberties, dates not examined; 7; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Rights of the Disabled, dates not examined; 8; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - AIDS and Civil Liberties - Litigation, dates not examined; 9; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Immigration Rights, dates not examined; 10; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Rights of Gays and Lesbians, dates not examined; 11; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Children's Rights, dates not examined; 12; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Women's Rights, dates not examined; 13; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Separation of Church and State, dates not examined; 14; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - National Security and Civil Liberties, dates not examined; 15; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - AIDS and Civil Liberties - Legislation, dates not examined; 16; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - International Standards and Domestic Civil Liberties, dates not examined; 17; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Worker's Rights, dates not examined; 18; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - ACLU Publications and Newsletters, dates not examined; 19; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Development Workshop, dates not examined; 20A-20E; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Public Education, dates not examined; 21; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Legislative Issues and Lobbying, dates not examined; 22A-20D; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Lawyers Meetings - Race/Gender, dates not examined; 23A-B; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Lawyers Meetings - Voting, Aids, New Strategies in Education, dates not examined; 24A; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Lawyers Meetings - Voting, Aids, New Strategies in Education, dates not examined; 24B; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Lawyers Meetings - Supreme Court Review, dates not examined; 25A-B; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Conference Banquet, dates not examined; 26A; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)
        - Conference Banquet, dates not examined; 26B; portion of 1 box (Box 2056)